* en

en

Privacy Policy
==============

##### Table of contents

##### Table of contents

[Introduction](#introduction) [Contact Details](#contact-details) [Definitions](#definitions) [What data do we collect about you and on what ground do we process it?](#what-do-we-collect) [How we use your data](#how-we-use-your-data) [Your privacy and legal rights](#your-privacy) [Disclosures of your personal data](#disclosures) [Marketing communications](#marketing-communications) [International transfers](#international-transfers) [Data security](#data-security) [Data retention](#data-retention) [Cookies](#cookies) [Third-party links](#third-party-links) [YouTube and Google](#youtube-and-google) [Automatic information](#automatic-information) [Public information](#public-information) [Links to other websites](#links-to-other-websites) [Privacy policy updates](#privacy-policy-updates) [Questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy policy](#questions)

Our Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of our Website, i.e. how we collect and process your personal data through the use of [www.inoreader.com](https://www.inoreader.com/). Any capitalized terms not defined in our Privacy Policy, have the meaning as specified in our Terms of Service.

### Introduction

By providing us with your data, you warrant to us that you are over 13 years of age. Innologica Ltd is the data controller and we are responsible for your personal data (referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy policy).

### Contact details

Full name of legal entity: Innologica Ltd

Email address: [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Postal address: 35 Boris Stefanov str. 1700 Sofia Bulgaria

It is very important that the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date. Please let us know if at any time your personal information changes by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) OR go to Preferences > Profile in Inoreader.

### Definitions

“Non-Personal Data" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Website with a web browser. It may also include publicly available information that is shared between you and others. “Personal data" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you with our Website (it does not include anonymised data). Personal data may include information such as your name, email address, password and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you.

### What data do we collect about you and on what ground do we process it?

Generally, you control the amount and type of data you provide to us when using our Website. We may process the following categories of personal data about you:

* Communication Data that includes any communication that you send to us whether that be through the contact form on our website, through email, text, social media messaging, social media posting or any other communication that you send us. We process this data for the purposes of communicating with you, for record keeping and for the establishment, pursuance or defence of legal claims. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to reply to communications sent to us, to keep records and to establish, pursue or defend legal claims.
* Customer Data that includes data relating to any purchases of goods and/or services such as your name, title, billing address, delivery address email address, phone number, contact details, purchase details and your card details. We process this data to supply the goods and/or services you have purchased and to keep records of such transactions. Our lawful ground for this processing is the performance of a contract between you and us and/or taking steps at your request to enter into such a contract.
* User Data that includes data about how you use our website and any online services, any data that you post for publication on our website or through other online services, and the profile pictures uploaded by our users, which we collect and store on our servers. We process this data to operate our website and ensure relevant content is provided to you, to ensure the security of our website, to maintain back- ups of our website and/or databases and to enable publication and administration of our website, other online services and business. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business.
* Technical Data that includes data about your use of our website and online services such as your IP address, your login data, details about your browser, length of visit to pages on our website, page views and navigation paths, details about the number of times you use our website, time zone settings and other technology on the devices you use to access our website. The source of this data is from our analytics tracking system. We process this data to analyse your use of our website, to administer and protect our business and website, to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and to understand the effectiveness of our advertising. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to enable us to properly administer our website and our business and to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.
* Marketing Data that includes data about your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences. We process this data to enable you to partake in our promotions such as competitions, prize draws and free give-aways, to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of this advertising. Our lawful ground for this processing is our legitimate interests which in this case are to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to decide our marketing strategy.
* We may use Customer Data, User Data, Technical Data and Marketing Data to deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you (including Facebook adverts or other display advertisements) and to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve you. Our lawful ground for this processing is legitimate interests which is to grow our business. We may also use such data to send other marketing communications to you. Our lawful ground for this processing is either consent or legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).
* We do not collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

Where we are required to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of the contract between us and you do not provide us with that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract (for example, to deliver goods or services to you). If you don't provide us with the requested data, we may have to cancel a product or service you have ordered but if we do, we will notify you at the time.

We will only use your personal data for a purpose it was collected for or a reasonably compatible purpose if necessary. For more information on this please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). In case we need to use your details for an unrelated new purpose we will let you know and explain the legal grounds for processing.

We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where this is required or permitted by law.

### How we use your data

We use the information we receive from you as follows:

* Customizing our website. We may use the Personal data you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize our Website for better user experience.
* Sharing information with affiliates and other third parties. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personal Data to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide your Personal Data to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Website (i.e. payment processors, Website hosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.
* Data aggregation. We retain the right to collect and use any Non Personal Data collected from your use of our Website and aggregate such data for internal analytics that improve our Website and Service. At no time is your Personal Data included in such data aggregations.

### Your privacy and legal rights

Innologica Ltd follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information. You will see terms in our Privacy Policy that are capitalized. These terms have meanings as described in the Definitions section below.

Under data protection laws you have rights in relation to your personal data that include the right to request access, correction, erasure, restriction, transfer, to object to processing, to portability of data and (where the lawful ground of processing is consent) to withdraw consent.

You can see more about these rights at: [https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-data-protection/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-data-protection/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/)

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive or refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you.

If you are not happy with any aspect of how we collect and use your data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues ([www.ico.org.uk](https://www.inoreader.com/www.ico.org.uk)). We should be grateful if you would contact us first if you do have a complaint so that we can try to resolve it for you.

### Disclosures of your personal data

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below:

* Service providers who provide IT and system administration services.
* Pro advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers
* Government bodies that require us to report processing activities.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### Marketing communications

Our lawful ground of processing your personal data to send you marketing communications is either your consent or our legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).

Under the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations, we may send you marketing communications from us if (i) you made a purchase or asked for information from us about our goods or services or (ii) you agreed to receive marketing communications and in each case you have not opted out of receiving such communications since. Under these regulations, if you are a limited company, we may send you marketing emails without your consent. However you can still opt out of receiving marketing emails from us at any time.

Before we share your personal data with any third party for their own marketing purposes we will get your express consent.

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences OR by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or OR by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) at any time.

If you opt out of receiving marketing communications this opt-out does not apply to personal data provided as a result of other transactions, such as purchases, warranty registrations etc.

### International transfers

We do not transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

### Data security

We have put in place security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used, altered, disclosed, or accessed without authorisation. We also allow access to your personal data only to those employees and partners who have a business need to know such data. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they must keep it confidential.

We have procedures in place to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach if we are legally required to.

### Data retention

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

When deciding what the correct time is to keep the data for we look at its amount, nature and sensitivity, potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure, the processing purposes, if these can be achieved by other means and legal requirements.

For tax purposes the law requires us to keep basic information about our customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data) for five years after they stop being customers.

In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

### Cookies

Our Website uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personal Data in Cookies. For more information about the cookies we use, please see [https://www.inoreader.com/cookie\_use](https://www.inoreader.com/cookie_use).

### Third-party links

This website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

### YouTube and Google

Inoreader uses the YouTube API services to provide certain functionalities. By using this service you acknowledge and agree to be bound by the YouTube Terms of Service and to the connected use of the Google Privacy Policy, which can be found through the following links: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and [https://www.youtube.com/t/terms](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms).

You can revoke Inoreader's access to your Google and YouTube data at any time via the Google security settings page at [https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions).

### Automatic information

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Service.

### Public information

You can choose from your profile settings to "Disable social features" or select which of your public information can be viewed by all users in reader or just your connections. Your shared items including comments. Import Subscriptions from another reader. You can import your subscriptions from Google Reader for example directly and we use only feeds without personal information.

### Links to other websites

Our Website contain links to other websites that are not under our direct control. These websites may have their own policies regarding privacy. We have no control of or responsibility for linked websites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. You access such linked Websites at your own risk. These websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information. In addition, these websites may contain a link to Websites of our affiliates. The websites of our affiliates are not subject to this Privacy Policy, and you should check their individual privacy policies to see how the operators of such websites will utilize your personal information.

### Privacy policy updates

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Website, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we determine. The method we chose is at our sole discretion. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.

### Questions about our privacy practices or this privacy policy

If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please [\[email protected\]](https://www.inoreader.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

##### With Inoreader, content comes to you the minute it's available. Follow websites, social media feeds, podcasts, blogs, and newsletters. Enjoy what’s important to you, all in one place.

With Inoreader, content comes to you the minute it's available. Follow websites, social media feeds, podcasts, blogs, and newsletters. Enjoy what's important to you, all in one place.

English

English

×

### Sign in

Email address: 

Please enter Email

Password 

Please enter password

 Remember me

Sign in

Or simply sign in with:

[](javascript:void() "Sign in with your Google account")[](javascript:void() "Sign in with your Apple account")[](https://www.inoreader.com/sso "Corporate login (SAML SSO)")

#### Create account

**With Inoreader, content comes to you.** Sign up to browse more than 5 000 000 sources and build the ultimate newsfeed!

Don't have an account?  

×

### Create account

Email address 

Please enter email

Password 

Please enter password

Create account

Or simply sign in with:

[](javascript:void() "Sign in with your Google account")[](javascript:void() "Sign in with your Apple account")[](https://www.inoreader.com/sso "Corporate login (SAML SSO)")

#### Sign in

**Already have an account?** Enter your profile and access your feeds now.

Already have an account?  

×

Request Quote

Name

Please enter name

Email

Please provide valid email

Company Optional

Industry Optional

Select from listMedia and PublishingPharmaceuticalsCybersecurityTelecommunicationsIT and SoftwareFinance and BankingTransport and LogisticsMarketing and PRPublic AuthoritiesInternational OrganizationsResearchEducation ServicesOther

Position Optional

Message

Please enter message

 I understand and accept the [Inoreader Privacy Policy](https://www.inoreader.com/tos)

You must accept the privacy policy

Send message

Your message has been sent. We'll get in touch as soon as possible. Be sure to follow our Facebook page and Twitter account so you always know what's up with your favorite news reader.
